折翼天使首部曲：魔咒之吻
有光之前便有天使
Before there was light there were angels.
这一刻黑暗
One moment darkness
下一刻荣耀的光华照亮天堂
the next, heaven was bright with glorious beings.
非常完美
It was perfect.
但好景不常
It did not last.
路西法背弃了神
Lucifer revolted against God.
天堂从此划分界线
A line was drawn in paradise.
战争开始
A war began.
天使们被迫作出选择
Every angel was forced to choose
天堂的神圣或者凡间的纷乱
the holiness of heaven or the chaos that roiled outside.
有一位天使拒绝选择
One angel refused
他相信唯一值得争取的
believing the only thing worth fighting for
是我们现在称为 "爱" 的力量
was a force we now call love.
这天使被逐出天堂
Cast out of heaven
然而他并不孤独
this angel did not fall alone.
每个还未作出选择的天使
Every angel who had yet to choose
都因神的愤怒而下堕
fell in a flash of almighty fury.
成为了折翼天使
These are the Fallen.
他们从天堂被流放
Exiled from heaven
到人间浪荡
they wander the earth
直至那叛逆天使
banished until the rebel angel
放弃爱而作出选择
abandons love and takes a side.
那是从前
That was then.
这是现今
This is now.
就是这间？
Is that it?
一定是
Must be.
"剑与十字学院"
爱你
Love you.
乖女儿
My baby.
如果我知道怎样能帮到你就好了
I just wish I knew how to help you.
没事的
I'll be fine.
你看
Look here.
小小意思
It's small.
希望你在生日有礼物拆
I wanted you to have something to open on your birthday.
多谢
Thank you.
我爱你
I love you.
拜拜 爸爸
Bye, Dad.
欢迎来到 "剑与十字学院"
Welcome to Sword and Cross Academy.
超过75年来 我们一直服务
For over 75 years we have served adolescents
因社会或情绪问题 无法适应…
who because of social and-or emotional challenges that they face
传统教学环境的青少年
have been unable to thrive in a traditional academic environment.
"剑与十字" 揉合大学预科
At Sword and Cross we combine college preparatory education
先进临床服务
cutting edge clinical services
及集中个人发展的
and diverse enrichment programs that focus on
多元化进修项目
personal growth.
这次你想怎么处置他？
Where do you want him this time?
先去那边等等
Through there.
我马上过来
I'll be right with you.
包括
Including
剑击 游泳
fencing, swimming
及使用我们著名的福勒图书馆
and the use of our world renowned Fowler Library.
创办人的哲学是基于核心原则…
Our founder's philosophy is based upon the core principles...
丢弃你的危险品
Now dump your hazards.
危险品？
Hazards?
酒精 毒品 武器
Alcohol. Drugs. Weapons of any type.
帮会物品或衣着
Gang related items or clothing.
音乐播放器 药丸 游戏机 电脑
Music players, tablets, gaming systems, laptops.
手机
Cell phones.
不 不 我需要手机
No no no, I need my phone.
每星期你有10分钟通电话特权
You get ten minutes of phone privileges once a week.
- 你在开玩笑吧 - 这是什么？
- You're kidding. - What's this?
- 不知道 是礼物 - 危险品
- I don't know, it's a present... - Hazard.
我赶时间 兰迪
Haven't got all day, Randy.
我就过来
I'll be right there. Arriane!
阿莉安 麻烦你带露西去宿舍
Could you show Lucinda to the dorms?
好 明白
Sure, I got it.
午饭后来取回行李
You can pick your bag up after lunch.
甘 你周末怎过？我洗耳恭听
So tell me about your weekend, Cam. I'm all ears.
- 阿莉安 - 露西
- Arriane. - Luce.
这次给他有限度的自由
We're going to keep him on a very short leash.
不用惩罚了
There's no need to press charges this time, Bill.
一切都在我掌控中
You know we've got this covered.
我们会好好看管他
We'll keep a good eye on him.
- 你最好远离甘 - 为什么？
- You're going to want to stay away from Cam. - Yeah, why's that?
他是个麻烦的家伙
He's trouble.
不是什么善类
Not the good kind.
给我看看你的时间表
Let me see your schedule.
很好 你跟我们一起
Good, you're with us.
- 我们？- 预科班
- Us? - Prep-track.
我们多数聚在一起
We tend to stick together.
大部份人都是精神科转来的
Most kids here are psych referrals.
遇着一个整天没弄湿自己
They're lucky to get through the day without wetting themselves
或没用铅笔袭击老师的便算幸运
or attacking a teacher because their pencils are unevenly sharpened.
不用怕 他们被隔开了
Don't be spooked, though. They keep them separate.
有严重精神问题的在三楼
All the serious mental defectives are up on the third floor.
个个都要吃药
It's one big pharmapalooza.
我到了 208号房
This is me. 208.
你几号房？
Where are you?
你玩我 是吗？
You're messing with me, right?
你是精神…
You're a psy...
明白
Okay.
喂
Hey.
对不起
Sorry.
谈谈你的幻觉 你叫它们做什么？
Tell me about your hallucinations. What do you call them?
影子
Shadows.
什么时候开始看到？
And they started when?
小时候
When I was little.
五 六岁吧 记不清楚
Five or six. I can't remember exactly.
现在仍看到？
And you still see them?
不 没看到一段时间
No. I haven't for a while.
告诉我 露西达
Tell me, Lucinda.
你觉得你为何要来到
Why do you think you're here
"剑与十字"？
at Sword and Cross?
问法官吧
Ask the judge.
我看过档案 知道法官的想法
I've read your file. I know what the judge thinks.
只是不明白你的决定
What I don't understand is your decision.
施医生说吃药后你情况会变得稳定
Doctor Segal says that on medication, you're stable.
没幻觉 没恐慌 没噩梦
No hallucinations. No paranoia. No nightmares.
我不是神经病
I'm not crazy, you know.
没人说你是
No. Nobody's saying you're crazy.
但人人都那样说
Everybody's saying that.
你知道只要你肯吃药 便可离开
Do you understand, that if you take your prescribed medication you can leave.
然后回家去 返回旧学校
Go home. Go back to your old school.
跟朋友一起
Be with your friends.
我不喜欢吃药后的感觉
I don't like the way they make me feel.
你拒绝的话 便要留下
But if you refuse, you need to be here
在这法院认可的感化院接受监管
in a court sanctioned treatment facility, under supervision.
即使被锁起来
Even if it means being locked up
我也要做自己而不假装妥协
I'd rather be me than pretend to be something I'm not just to fit in.
你有机会过正常生活的
You have a chance at a normal life.
真可怜 她懵然不知自己的处境
Poor thing. She has no idea what she's in for.
也许这次会不同
Maybe it'll be different this time.
你知道什么？
You know something I don't?
没什么 有改变总是好的
It'd just be nice for a change, that's all.
好 就多加点乐趣吧
Alright, let's make it interesting.
20赔1 露西被火吞噬 一如以往
Twenty to one Luce goes down in flames, just like always.
我下注100
I'm in for a hundred.
- 阿莉安 - 什么？
- Arriane! - What?
- 嘉比？- 太残酷吧
- Gabbe? - It's cruel.
这不是游戏 罗伦
This isn't a game, Roland.
或者它是
Maybe it is.
周而复始
Here we go again.
心灵自成一片天地 在其间
The mind is its own place and in itself
天堂可以化为地狱
can make a Hell of Heaven.
那是什么？
What's that?
密尔顿的《失乐园》
Milton. Paradise Lost.
- 你是露西达普斯？- 是
- You're Lucinda Price? - Yeah.
我是苏菲亚 是你的宗教哲学班导师
I'm Miss Sophia. You're in my Philosophy of Religion class.
- 你来取书？- 对
- Did you come for your books? - Mm-hmm.
数学 英国文学 化学 宗教历史
Pre-calc, English lit, Chemistry, Religion and History.
还欠一本
Oh, still missing one.
不介意吧？它在特别藏书室
Would you mind? It's in special collections.
没问题
Sure.
很高兴认识你 露西
Ah, it's a pleasure to meet you, Luce.
多谢你
Thanks.
你好
Hi.
喂 等等
Hey, wait.
你掉了这个
You dropped this.
可恶
Shit!
你吓到我了
You scared me.
好吧
Alright.
你这可怜虫
You poor thing.
- 离谱 - 你跌倒了？
- Jeez. - Oh, did you fall?
有受伤吗？
Are you hurt?
- 我没事 - 不 你有事
- I'm fine. - No you're not.
你这么令人讨厌 又怎么会没事
You've never been less fine in your whole nauseating existence.
你来这儿是个错误
Coming here was a bad choice.
若我得罪了你 我道歉
Listen, if I did something to upset you, I'm sorry...
你令我反胃
You make me sick.
你什么都不是
You're nothing.
以为搔首弄姿 世界就会停止？
You bat your lashes and flick your hair and expect the whole world to come to a stop.
你根本不认识我
You don't even know me.
我知道你是个杀人的疯妇
I know you're a murdering little psycho.
喂 停手
Hey! Break it up!
疯妇 你应该挂个警告牌
Psycho bitch. You should come with a warning label.
这么快就来闹事了
That was quick.
- 她… - 你想说是她先挑的事
- She... - Don't tell me she started it.
我当然知道
I'm sure she did.
但并不代表你要掉入圈套
But that doesn't mean you have to take the bait.
你说得对 很抱歉
You're right. I'm sorry.
打架可以被开除
Fighting is grounds for expulsion.
对你来说是要转去国立精神病院
Which for you would mean a transfer to the state psych hospital.
你想那样吗？
Is that what you want?
不
No.
姑念你第一天到这里 未熟校规
Since today is your first day and I'm guessing you've yet to read the code of conduct
我只罚你打扫庭园
I'll just give you yard duty.
你呢？跟我来
And you? You come with me.
你知道没通行证是不准进来的吗？
You know you're not supposed to be in here without a pass.
我只是…
I just, ah...
不… 跟你说笑罢了
Oh no no no, that was a joke.
- 噢 - 抱歉
- Oh. - I'm sorry.
天啊
Oh gosh.
不好笑吗？
Oh. Not funny?
只是今天很难捱
It's just been a really rough day.
对 欢迎来到 "剑与＋字"
Yeah. Welcome to Sword and Cross.
- 这地方… - 十足是疯人院
- This place is... - Crazy.
我是潘妮云锡高洛活 叫我潘妮
I'm Pennyweather Van Syckle-Lockwood. You can call me Penn.
好
Okay.
你是露西达普斯 人人都叫你露西
And you are Lucinda Price, but everyone calls you Luce.
由多佛转来 平均分4.2
Transferred here from Dover with a 4.2.
很厉害
Impressive.
你怎知道？
How did you know that?
噢 我像跟踪狂这么变态？
Shoot. Was that stalkery?
有一点
A little bit, yeah.
不好意思
Sorry.
其实这学校好小 小到一眼能看到全部
See the thing is, this is a really small school. Like really, really small.
这里小到没太多事发生
Like infinitesimally small, and not a lot happens here.
不像多佛 你新来 既聪明又美丽
It's not like Dover, and you're the new girl and you're smart and you're pretty
相信会吸引很多人注意
so I'm guessing that you're going to be the centre of a lot of attention
有好有坏
both positive and negative.
好极了
Great.
告诉你
Tell you what.
我走了 让你做你的事
I'm gonna go, let you do your thing
希望你大人有大谅…
and then maybe if you're feeling forgiving you can...
忘掉我在浴室打扰你
forget the whole me accosting you in the bathroom with too much information
以及胡言乱语说一堆
when you just want to be alone and then rambling on and on
因我不懂得闭嘴
because I don't know know how to stop myself
就像现在
from talking situation that's happening right now
你肯给我机会吗？
and give me another chance?
我走了
I'll go now.
- 潘妮 - 什么事
- Hey Penn? - Yeah?
可以带我回宿舍吗？我有点迷路
Do you mind showing me back to the dorms? I'm a little bit lost.
当然可以
Sure.
谢谢
Thanks.
假如天使真的在地上与我们同行？
What if angels actually walked among us right now, here on earth?
那是折翼天使的故事
That's the story of The Fallen.
天使被逐出天堂
Angels cast out of heaven
贬落人间与我们凡人共处
condemned to live their lives alongside us mere mortals.
被驱逐 因他们不能
Banished, because they failed to pick a side
在路西法与天堂之战中选边站
in Lucifer's war against Heaven.
谁知道这场仗是关于什么？
Who can tell me what the war in Heaven was about?
杜特
Todd?
美善对邪恶？
Good versus evil?
不 太简单了
No, that's too simplistic.
路西法是神的宠儿
Lucifer was God's favourite.
最亮的光
His brightest light.
他为何要背弃神？
What caused him to turn from God?
谁知道？
Anyone?
被女朋友甩了
'Cause his girlfriend dumped him.
其他天使下场如何？
What happened to the other angels?
支持撒旦的被打落地狱
Those that sided with Satan were banished to Hell.
只有忠心的留在天堂
Only the faithful remained in heaven.
没有作出选择的就被逐出天堂
The angels that didn't choose, they were cast out.
成为折翼天使
They are the Fallen.
被迫在人间生活
Forced to walk the earth
有些保留了天使本色
some of the Fallen retained their angelic nature
悔过然后等待返回天堂的机会
repented and wait for the chance to return to Heaven.
有些与路西法为伍
Others aligned themselves with Lucifer
在捣蛋混乱中寻找快乐
finding pleasure in mischief and chaos.
但两者都离不开这世界
But neither group can leave this world
因为他们之一
because of one of their own.
那叛逆天使
The rebel angel.
他拒绝加入战争的任何一方
He rejected both sides of the war
神也好 路西法也好
God and Lucifer alike
他只寻求人类的爱
all in his pursuit of human love.
其余的折翼天使
The other fallen angels
都要留在人间
must remain here on earth
直至他在这场唯一的战争中选边站
until he chooses a side in the only war that has ever been waged.
我们周围每天仍见到的战争
The war we still see every day raging all around us.
返主日学你也听过吧？
But surely you learned some of this in Sunday school?
不 我没有去教会
No, I didn't go to church growing up.
真的吗？
Really?
是 我父母不太虔诚
Yeah, my parents aren't really religious.
你从没受洗？
So, you were never baptized?
没有
Um, no.
那场仗是否已打完？
Is it supposed to be over, the war?
我指神学上
I mean, theologically speaking
假如魔鬼仍在生
if the Devil is still alive
谁可阻挡他再挑起事端？
What's to stop him trying from trying again?
问得好
Excellent question.
还有人下注吗？
So, any more takers on that bet?
有
Yep.
继续收 罗伦
Keep them rolling, Roland.
露西 真可怜
Luce, you poor thing.
没事吧？
Are you okay?
发生什么事？有人受伤吗？
What is going on here? Is anyone hurt?
没有 我没事
No really, I'm fine.
伙食很好
The food is fine.
- 有事吗？- 没事 乖女儿
- Anything? - Anything, sweetie.
你的橙皮玉桂煎饼
加忌廉香蕉 想起就…
Definitely your orange cinnamon pancakes with whipped cream with bananas. That sounds...
喂
Hey!
你煲电话粥啊？快挂断
What's taking so long? Come on.
我要用
I need it.
妈？妈？
Mom? Mom?
分配时间用完 分配时间用完
Allocated time completed. Allocated time completed.
又要等一星期才可以跟他们通话
I just can't believe I have to wait a whole week to talk to them.
连说再见也没机会
You know, I didn't even get a chance to say goodbye.
给你用我星期二的分配时间
You can have my time on Tuesday.
不用
No.
没关系 我用不着
Yeah, I'm not gonna use it.
我来了六年 所有朋友都在此
I've been here six years. Everyone I know is here
有兴趣聊天的都已在这间房
and everyone I'm interested in talking to is in this room.
你父母呢？
What about your parents?
我一直想问…
I've been meaning to ask.
我为何被送来？
How I ended up here?
你不想说就算 无所谓的
You don't have to tell me. It's not a big deal.
爸妈离婚后
Well after my parents got divorced
两人都不想要我
neither of them really wanted me around so
决定送我入寄宿学校
they decided that boarding school was in my best interest.
当妈看到那本小册子
And as soon as my Mom saw that brochure
看到有骑马游水诸如此类的活动
the one with the kids riding horses and swimming and stuff
就决定了
that was it.
不再找 替我报名 我便来了
The search was over, I was enrolled and here I am.
所以你不是有盗窃癖
燥郁 厌食或自残？
So you're not a kleptomaniac, manic depressive, anorexic cutter?
统统没有
No.
我的病情更严重
My diagnosis is much worse
恐怕没救了
and, I'm afraid, untreatable.
我有计划书
I have TDP.
计划书？
TDP?
从没见过这么冷漠的父母
Tragically Disinterested Parents.
是 我父母真的很差劲
Yeah, my parents suck.
但你有个后援
But there's a pool.
But there is a pool.
你想跟我开玩笑
You've gotta be kidding me.
别告诉我
Don't tell me.
你堕入爱河？
Is Cam in love?
那样你很难做
That could make things difficult for you.
别忘了你为谁工作
Just don't forget who you work for.
丹尼尔
Daniel.
昨天没机会多谢你
I didn't get a chance to say thanks yesterday.
小意思
Don't mention it.
总之谢谢你
Well thank you anyway.
还有一件事我不好意思问
There's one more thing I'm a little embarrassed to even ask but...
那么别问
Well then don't.
我决定问 现在就问
Well I've committed now. I'm just going to go for it.
你很面熟
It's just you seem really familiar to me.
我们之前好像见过面
Like I know you from somewhere.
- 有可能吗？- 不
- Is that possible? - No.
见过的话我会记得你
I'd remember you.
我一直想…
Because I keep thinking that...
我要走了 迟点见
I've gotta go, alright? I'll see you later.
谢谢
Thank you.
喂 新来的 这几天很充实吧
Hey new girl. Pretty eventful first few days.
已计划逃学？
Already planning your escape?
考虑中
Yeah, considering it.
吃早餐吗？
You ah, you want some breakfast?
很诱人 但上课要迟到了
That's tempting, but I'm actually running late to class.
迟到总比不到好
It's better never than late.
味道很好
This is really good.
哪儿来的？
Where's it from?
从教员休息室偷来的
I stole it from the faculty lounge.
他们有很棒的咖啡机
They have a pretty decent espresso machine.
你没得救了
You're incorrigible.
人人都这么说
That's what they tell me.
你不同意？
You don't agree?
我知道自己想怎样
I just know what I like.
所以不惜犯规去争取？
And you don't mind breaking the rules to get it.
嗯…
Well
如果是值得的话
if the risk is worth the reward
有何不可？
I don't see why not.
你呢？
What about you?
你若是守规矩就不会进 "剑与十字"吧
You don't end up at Sword and Cross by following the rules.
你内心都是叛逆的？
You got a little rebel in you?
我只是被误解
I'm just misunderstood.
不 我看到
No, I see it.
你有火花
You got a spark.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
你是那种不理会别人想法
认为对就去做的人
Means you're the kind of person who'd rather do what's right than what you're told.
是爱找麻烦的那种
It means you're trouble.
你以为很了解我？
You think you know me, huh?
我了解我喜欢的人
I know what I like.
到点了
Time's up.
星期五罗伦搞派对
Roland's having a party this Friday.
- 是吗？- 只是普通派对
- Yeah? - It's just casual.
- 你可以带朋友来 - 好
- You can bring a friend. - Okay.
我们周末聚会都会相互倾诉
Bunch of us get together at the end of the week to blow off some steam.
谢谢
Thanks.
你不是上这节课吗？
Aren't you in this class?
我全都会背
Oh, I've heard it all before.
准备 开始
En garde! Allez!
他们有考虑清楚吗？
How well did they think this through?
把武器交给情绪不受控
You know, giving weapons to heavily medicated teenagers
服过量药的青少年
with poor impulse control and anger issues.
停
Halt!
好 换拍挡 史柏斯 到你
Alright, change partners. Sparks, you're up.
普斯 看你有否留心
Price, let's see if you've been paying attention.
记得我怎么教你的？
Remember what I showed you?
不太记得了
Not really.
准备
En garde!
开始
Allez!
不算太差
That wasn't terrible
对一个菜鸟来说
considering it was just your first time.
好
Alright.
交换拍挡
Switch partners.
格里戈里 过来
Grigori. Come on over.
准备
En garde!
开始
Allez!
很好
Very good.
再来 准备
One more. En garde.
开始
Allez!
格里戈里 停
Grigori, halt.
停
Halt!
停啊
你们两个 停啊
Both of you, halt!
最多一星期
I give it a week.
洗礼会对她有影响吗？
What about the whole baptism thing? Could that affect her?
细节不重要
The details don't matter.
丹尼尔总是执迷不悟
Grigori always finds something to obsess over but it never makes a difference.
你们只要放开怀抱 接受露西的死亡
Now y'all just need to relax and accept that Luce is gonna die
任何人都无法阻止这件事
and there's nothing you or Daniel or Miss Sophia can do to stop it.
还以为你从未试过
I thought you'd never done this before?
的确未试过
I haven't.
是身体自然反应
My body just took over.
好像知道怎做
Like I knew exactly what to do.
吓？
Huh.
真奇怪 你试过这种情况吗？
It was weird. Have you ever felt that?
有 读三角几何时
Yeah, I was kinda like that with trigonometry.
起初一切都很轻易
It all just fell into place so at first I was like
还自以为是个天才
'wow, I'm a genius. '
后来才记得原来去年读过
But then I remembered that we covered it last year so I guess that's not as impressive.
你迷上了他？
You got it bad, huh?
不 不是那样
No, it's not like that.
也有可能是
Well, maybe it is.
我对丹尼尔有些感觉
It's just I have these feelings about Daniel.
好像之前已经认识他
Like I know him.
认识了好久的那种
Like I've known him for a really long time.
可能是幼稚园同学之类
Yeah, maybe you guys went to preschool together or something.
我问他是否认识我 他说不
Well I asked him if we'd met before and he said no
然后调头走了 真奇怪
and he basically ran away. It was strange.
对啊
Yeah.
肯定有点奇怪…
Something definitely not quite... hmm.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
假如你告诉别人我说了什么
I can get in a lot of trouble if you tell anybody
我会很麻烦
what I'm about to say to you, okay?
我不会
I won't.
没课时我会去校务处帮忙
So I volunteer in the office for my free period
虽然听起来很老套 但其实很好玩
which I know sounds totally lame but is actually kind of cool and fun
又非常的奇特
in its own weird way, sort of.
原来兰迪对电脑一窍不通
Turns out Randy is totally useless when it comes to computers.
所以请本小姐帮忙做一些简单的如
So he asks yours truly to do the most basic tasks like
找档案及刺猬打喷嚏的片段等
find files on his desktop and search for videos of sneezing hedgehogs or whatever.
换言之
Meaning
我可以拿到所有人的入学纪录
I have full access to everybody's academic records.
我看过丹尼尔的档案
I've looked at Daniel's file.
空空如也
It's empty.
没地址 没紧急联络人 什么都没有
He's got no home address, no emergency contact, nothing.
- 这件怎么样？好啊
- Do you like this? - Yeah.
那群人都是
It's the same with all those kids.
所有的人都不对劲
There's just something not quite right about that whole group.
没听过他们提及家人或以前的学校
You never hear them talk about their families or their old schools.
经常不上课而且像是旧相识
They barely ever go to class and it's like they all knew each other from before.
等等 什么意思？
Wait, who do you mean?
丹尼尔最先来
Daniel arrived first.
去年初他转过来 然后是嘉比
He transferred at the beginning of last year and then Gabbe.
他身边那个高挑金发妹？
The tall blonde that's always hanging around him?
是 含糖量85%
Yep, 85 percent confectionary sugar by volume.
之后是阿莉安
Then Arriane.
她第一天带我到处看
Oh yeah, she showed me around my first day.
莫莉 病入膏育
And Molly. Serious defective.
以及罗伦 不知他怎通过验尿的
And Roland, I have literally no idea how he passes his weekly pee test
最后是春天才转过来的未来囚犯阿甘
and then Mr. Future 25 Years to Life, Cam, transferred in last spring.
还有苏菲亚小姐
Miss Sophia, too.
今年才来 目中无人 只看到乖学生
She's new this year and totally ignores everyone except her favourites.
你有什么结论？
Well what do you make of it?
这真的难到我了
Beats me.
- 意想不到 - 什么？
- I can't believe it. - What?
竟然可以去罗伦的派对
I'm actually going to one of Roland's parties.
两位靓女
Oh, don't you two look lovely?
过奖
Thanks.
你都是 一向都是
You do too. As always.
真想亲你一口
Aren't you sweet.
我有点讨厌她 是不是不好？
Is it wrong that I kind of hate her?
因为她太完美 金发
Why, because she's a flawless, honey-scented, spray tanned,
古铜肤色超棒的身材 迷人的笑容
bikini waxed manicured blond-fembot who's always smiling
这一刻你们正在热吻？
and is at this moment kissing your crush?
或者是
Yeah, pretty much that.
可能不对 但我可以理解
It might be wrong, but I totally get it.
有人要酒吗？
Anybody order drinks?
我仍在想你为什么来这儿
I'm still trying to figure out how you ended up here.
你请我来的 记得吗？
Well you invited me, remember.
我不是指这个派对
That's not what I meant.
其余的人很明显
With the rest of us it's obvious, right?
嗑药
Drugs.
蓄意破坏
Vandalism.
抑郁
Depression.
发花痴
Nymphomania.
你为什么会被送来这种地方？
So why did you end up at a place like this?
可能我不像外表看的那么单纯
Maybe I'm not as innocent as I look.
- 你好 - 嗨
- Hello. - Hi.
莲花牌外套？
Is that a Flying Lotus jacket?
对
Yeah.
你是个时尚的人
You are such a hipster.
不是跟风的那种
In... in a good way, I mean.
你不是在耍帅
Like you know, it's not like you're trying to be cool.
但真的很酷
Like you're actually cool.
哗
Wow.
我经常被人说三道四
I've been accused of a lot of things in my life
但从没有人讲过我帅
but never that.
- 喂 - 谢谢
- Hey. - Oh, hey. Thank you.
给我的吗？
Oh, is that for me?
太棒了 谢谢你
Amazing. Thank you so much. Thank you.
别客气
Sure.
唔…
Um...
那么…
So...
看演出买的 或者是…
Is it from a show, or...?
是 他现场更劲爆
Yeah. He's amazing live.
我在阿什维尔看他和特贝斯
I saw him in Asheville with Teebs.
不是嘛 特贝斯是我的至爱
Get out of it. Teebs is my favourite post-Dilla artist.
雷猫改变我人生
Well Thundercat changed my life.
可能除了雷猫
Well no, except maybe for Thundercat.
听过阳光混音版吗？
Have you heard the Daylight remix?
那低音部份
That bass.
对
Exactly.
非常完美
Yes.
痛苦回忆？
Bad memories?
还在想念他？
So do you still think about him?
谁？
Who?
你杀的男孩 崔维尔
The boy you killed. Trevor.
高高的 很有型的
You know, tall, easy on the eyes.
起码和你在一起前还是
Well at least he was before he hooked up with you.
现在懒得看到他
Now he's not so much to look at.
你怎么知道他的事？
How do you know about him?
- 我知道你很多事的疯妇 - 拿开那东西
- I know a lot about you, Crazy Luce. - Get that away from me.
我比你更了解你自己
I'll bet I know you better than you know yourself.
你不喜欢火 但它很喜欢你
For someone who doesn't like fire, it sure does seem to like you.
够了
That's enough!
闭嘴 小心我在你脸留个像你背脊上一样的疤
Shut up, Arri, before I give you a scar on your face to match the one on your back.
走开 莫莉
Back off, Molly.
- 没事吧？- 我没事
- Are you okay? - Yeah, I'm fine.
你做什么？
What are you doing?
跟你那疯女友玩一下嘛
Just having some fun with your psycho girlfriend.
别搞露西
Stay away from Luce.
听到吗？
You hear me?
你知道自己在做什么吗 甘？
Oh, you've lost track, Cam.
你一向想要得不到的东西
You always want what you can't have.
这次她是我的
This time she's mine.
放开我
Lay off me!
外太空肯定有生物
There's definitely life in outer space!
露西在哪？
Hey! Where's Luce?
不知道 还以为她跟你在一起
Um, I don't know. I thought that she was with you.
好吧
Okay.
她不需要你帮忙
She doesn't need your kind of help.
谁来保护她？你呀？
Who's gonna protect her, you?
你们两个情敌放松点吧 这是派对
You know, you lovebirds need to relax, huh? It's a party.
我突然觉得很累
You know, I'm feeling pretty tired all of a sudden, actually.
我想回去
I think I'm just gonna go.
你要我陪你吗？
You want me to walk with you?
不用 你留下吧
No, it's okay. You should stay.
有人吗？
Hello?
莫莉
Molly.
莫莉 出来 我知道是你
Molly, come on. I know it's you.
崔维尔在哪？
Where's Trevor?
对不起
I'm so sorry.
你做过什么？怪物
What did you do, you freak!
是我的错
It's my fault.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
第一个星期在 "剑与十字" 过得如何？
So tell me, how was your first week at Sword and Cross?
不错
Fine.
没事要报告？
No incidents to report?
有没有幻觉及发噩梦？
Visions? Nightmares?
没有
No.
那些 "影子" 呢？
What about your shadows?
好
Good.
有什么不妥？
What's wrong?
没有
Nothing.
我无法抗拒
I just can't get past it.
什么？
What?
我有种认识你的感觉
This feeling that I know you.
我们不是已讲过？
Haven't we been through this?
是 但…
Yeah, but...
我不信你
I don't believe you.
我们之间有些微妙的感觉
There is something between us.
你也感觉到吧
And you feel it too, don't you?
好吧
Alright. Okay.
你说对了 我该向你坦白
You're right. I should have just told you the truth.
我知道…
It's...
我对你不太友善
Like I realise I haven't been very warm towards you, and...
简直差劲
You've been a real dick.
是的… 但相信我
Yeah, but believe me.
不是因为你做过了什么
You've got to know it's not because of anything you've done.
而是有个女孩…
See, there's this girl...
嘉比？
Gabbe?
什么？不…
What? No.
不是嘉比 是另一个
No, not Gabbe. No, just someone else. Another girl.
虽然我不再和她在一起 但…
I guess you could say I'm not with her anymore, but
我仍爱她
I still love her.
我想说的是…
What I'm trying to say is...
你好乱 我最好不要再麻烦你了？
You're a mess and I'm better off without you?
大概是吧
Something like that.
没那么简单
It's not that simple.
人的感觉控制不了
You can't tell someone how to feel.
对
Yeah.
但愿这次不一样
I wish things could be different.
喂 别走
Hey! Don't go.
原来你在这儿 我很担心你
There you are. I was worried about you.
在派对上你没说再见就走掉了
You left the party without saying goodbye.
有事吗？
What's wrong?
露西？
Luce?
停啊 回答我一下
Stop! Talk to me!
昨晚我跟莫莉聊天
I had an interesting conversation with Molly last night.
是啊…
Okay.
她道知我很多事
She knew things about me.
包括我没向人透露的事
Things I haven't shared with anyone.
然后呢？
And...?
有人跟她讲过我的事
Someone's been talking to her.
应该有人看过我档案
Someone who's read my file.
对 那样合情合理
Oh right, 'cause that makes perfect sense.
我把你出卖给一个无情无义
I betrayed your trust to a ruthless, soulless, unimaginative bully
肮脏 出口伤人的八婆 为了什么？
with suspect hygiene and poor language skills in exchange for what?
难道为了免费打耳洞和犯人纹身？
Oh, two free body piercings and a prison tattoo.
还以为能混过去 但被你识穿了
I was sure I'd get away with it, but you caught me.
起码你够胆承认
Well, at least you're big enough to admit it.
有什么问题？说实话
What's wrong? Really?
你看过我档案 是吗？
You have read my file, haven't you?
当然
Of course.
你知道…
So then you know about...
那些影子？
Your shadows?
你仍然看到？
Do you still see them?
是
Yeah.
如今都能看到？
Do you see them right now?
不 但来这里后越来越严重了
No. But since I've been here they've gotten a lot worse.
我好怕啊…
And I'm scared.
怕再会有人受伤
I'm scared somebody's going to get hurt.
不 别胡思乱想
No, don't be ridiculous.
我没有
I'm not.
崔维尔站在那里
Trevor was just standing there.
他就站在那里
He was just standing there
- 我们… - 告诉我事发的经过
- and we... - Okay. Tell me... tell me exactly what happened.
崔维尔整学年都当我透明的
Trevor acted like I didn't exist all year
突然在派对上追求我
and then suddenly at this party he was flirting with me.
跟我到小屋去
Come up to the cabin with me.
我很想感觉一次…
Just one time I wanted to feel
正正常常的…
normal.
- 喝点酒？- 好
- You want a drink? - Sure.
听到吗？
Did you hear that?
崔维尔 真的只有我们？
Trevor, are you sure that we're alone?
露西
Luce.
放松点
Relax.
不
No.
停 停呀 放开我
Stop. Stop. Get off. Get off!
- 搞什么东西？- 拜托你快点走
- What the hell? - Please, get out of here.
发生什么事了？
What's going on?
不… 不要
No. No!
露西？
Luce?
那影子前所未有的大
The shadows were bigger than ever.
突然一切被炸开了
And then suddenly everything exploded.
我不知怎么逃脱的 但崔维尔逃不过
And I don't know how but I was outside and Trevor didn't make it.
崔维尔
Trevor!
崔维尔在哪？告诉我
Where's Trevor? Tell me.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
你做过什么？怪物
What did you do, you freak?
是我的错 对不起
It's my fault. I'm so sorry.
崔维尔
Trevor!
他死了 因为我有问题
And he's dead because there's something wrong with me.
很高兴你想做我的朋友
And I'm really glad you want to be my friend
但你要离我远点 因我很危险
but you should stay away from me because I'm dangerous.
你有想过要他死吗？
Did you want him to die?
没有
No.
你有想过伤害他吗？
Did you try to hurt him?
没有
No.
那么就不是你错了
Well then it's not your fault.
不必孤立自己 露西 你需要朋友
You don't need to be alone, Luce. You need a friend.
等我来帮你
Let me help you.
为什么？
Why?
因为朋友要互相帮忙
Because that's what friends do.
上课讨论过路西法因骄傲而堕落
Last time we were discussing how it was Lucifer's pride that led to the fall.
好
Yes.
谁懂得翻译？
So who can translate?
（拉丁文）
Humilitas homines sanctis
angelis similes facit
（拉丁文）
et superbia ex angelis demones facit.
有人明白什么意思吗？
Anyone?
骄傲令天使沦为魔鬼
It was pride that turned angels into devils.
那是什么 露西？
What was that, Luce?
谦卑令人类化为天使
It is humility that makes men as angels.
骄傲令天使沦为魔鬼
It was pride that turned angels into devils.
我们有个拉丁文专家
We have a Latin scholar in our midst.
不 我从来没有…
No, I've never...
只是猜测
It was just a guess.
跟那叛逆天使有何关系呢？
So how does that relate to the rebel angel?
因为他的骄傲及对追求爱情的执迷
Wasn't it his pride, his stubborn pursuit of love over God
令折翼天使们被困在人间 不是吗？
that led to the Fallen being trapped on earth?
阿莉安
Arriane?
我厌倦你扭曲宗教寓言来满足自己
I'm tired of listening to you twist these religious fables to fit your own beliefs.
你将故事说成爱是种选择
You tell this story of yours as is love was a choice.
我不管你有何想法
I don't care for your tone.
可能你只是不满叛逆天使拣错对象
Maybe you're just pissed the rebel angel chose the wrong girl.
你出去
Get out.
乐意之至
Gladly.
我宁可永远在地狱燃烧
I'd rather burn in hell for all eternity
也不想再听你那些自大的废话
than have to listen to one more second of your pious self-satisfied ravings.
精彩绝伦
That was kind of awesome.
对
Yeah.
她会被罚停课？
Do you think she'll get suspended?
也未必会留学
I doubt she even gets detention.
那班人总有办法脱身的
Those kids get away with everything.
我忘了拿外套 马上就过来
Hey, I forgot my sweater. I'll catch up with you guys.
好
Okay.
听我说 你要留心阿甘
Listen to me. You've got to keep your eye on Cam.
你说什么？
What are you talking about?
雕像的事不是意外 她有危险
I don't believe the statue was an accident. She's in danger.
事发前我看到他在楼上
I saw him on the upper floor just before it happened.
他为什么要那样做？
Why would he do that?
你听到的 她没有受洗过
You heard. She isn't baptized.
她需要我们保护 她…
She needs our protection. She's...
不好意思 我忘了拿外套
Sorry, I just... I forgot my sweater.
我去跟她谈谈
I'll go talk to her.
露西
Hey Luce!
等等
Wait.
什么事？
What?
- 你想怎样？- 没什么
- What do you want? - Nothing.
想跟你一起走
I just thought maybe we could walk together.
哦…
Oh.
好的
Sure.
上课时你画的是什么？
What were you working on in class today?
没什么 只是…
Nothing. It's ah...
图画及故事
sort of a graphic novel.
哪种故事？
What kind of story?
算是浪漫爱情的…
I guess you could call it a romance.
有大团圆结局？
Does it have a happy ending?
不知道
I don't know.
你不知结局怎样？
You don't know how it ends?
不 还不知道
No, not yet.
老实说 有点闭塞
I'm sort of stuck, to be honest.
说出来 我想听下
Well let's hear it. Tell me your story.
不… 这样不太好
No. No, I don't think that's a good idea.
不好？
No?
我也许能帮到你呢
Maybe I could help you with the ending.
好吧
Okay.
故事讲个男孩和女孩
It's about this boy and this girl
他们深爱对方
and they love each other more than anything
但永远无法在一起
but they can never be together.
为什么？
Why?
因为有这诅咒
Because there's this curse.
他们每隔17年相遇
Every seventeen years they meet
然后堕入爱河
and they fall in love
在最快乐的时候 女孩会死掉
and then just when they're happiest, the girl dies.
这是个悲剧？
So it's a tragedy?
那男孩怎样？
What happens to the boy?
他一直等待
He waits.
不老 不变心
He doesn't age or change.
仍在深爱着她
He remains in love.
多年过去了 她终于回来了
Years pass, and eventually she returns.
同一个女孩？
The same girl?
她变了
She's changed.
有新的名字 新的家庭
She has a new name, new family.
对他完全没有记忆
She has no memory of him
但他知道是她
but he knows it's her.
她的灵魂
It's her soul
转世
reincarnated.
他们再次堕入爱河
And they fall in love.
一如以往
Always.
每次都有些不同
I mean, each time it's slightly different.
无数的版本 但结局都一样
There are infinite versions but the end is always the same.
只需轻轻一吻
But then all it takes is a kiss
她便会消失
and she's gone.
谁诅咒他们？
Who put the curse on them?
魔鬼本人
It was the devil himself.
他妒忌他们的爱 所以搞了破坏
He was jealous of their love, so he tried to break it.
总有办法解决吧？
There has to be something they can do, right?
他试过一切
He's tried everything.
寻找她
He tries looking for her
然后避开她
then tries to avoid her.
尝试打破令人心碎的宿命
Tries to run away from the inevitable heartbreak.
但诅咒总是死缠不放
But the curse always finds a way, no matter what.
你故事中的女孩
The girl in your story.
是你在泳池提过的那个她？
Is she the one you mentioned at the pool?
就是你仍深爱的女孩？
The girl you're still in love with?
对 她是灵感来源
She's the inspiration, yeah.
就是这女孩？
This girl?
被你发现了
Alright, you got me. It's um...
我借用你做她的转世
I was using you for her current incarnation.
这儿该是巴黎
This is meant to be Paris.
1723年
In 1723.
很傻吧
It's stupid.
为什么会是我？
Why me?
因为你很漂亮
Because you're beautiful.
但双眼画花了
But I messed up the eyes.
你双眼总有种魔力
There's always been something about your eyes.
有什么不妥？
What's wrong?
没什么
Nothing.
你去过这地方？
Tell me about this place. Have you been there before?
有关系吗？
Does it matter?
- 有 - 为什么？
- Yes. - Why?
我从来没有旅行过
I've never travelled before.
没有离开过本土
I've never even left the country.
但我知道画中那处往右有间咖啡店
But I know that there's a caf? just off to the right
雨后会有茉莉花气味
and I know it smells like jasmine after it rains.
那店主老伯很爱狗 但对太太很差
And I know that the old man that runs the caf? is kind to his dog and he's cruel to his wife
我知道因为我去过
and I know these things because I've been there.
我和你一起去过
And I've been there with you.
露西 别这样
Oh, Luce, come on.
不…
Don't.
不要说我疯了
Don't tell me that I'm crazy.
露西 这只是幅画
Luce, its' a drawing, alright?
是个虚构的故事
It's a story, that's all.
你在说谎
You're lying.
我很想告诉你 你想要知道的
I wish I could tell you what you want to hear.
但抱歉
I'm sorry.
吹吧
Blow.
生日快乐 露西
Happy birthday, Luce.
你怎么知道？
How'd you know?
许了什么愿？
Did you make a wish?
不能说 会不灵验的
I can't tell you. It won't come true.
没关系
Oh, that's okay.
我知道你许了什么愿
I already know what you wished for.
你知道？
Oh yeah?
我想要什么？
What'd I wish for?
答案
Answers.
你想知道真相
You want the truth.
八点拱门见 我会和盘托出
Meet me at the arches at eight and I'll tell you everything.
还有…
And Luce?
穿的漂亮点
Wear something nice.
派对时间
It's party time.
看看你
"17岁生日快乐 爱你的妈和爸"
Look at you.
哗
Oh, wow.
是你的？
Is it yours?
只限今晚
For tonight.
你怎么弄到的？
How'd you manage that?
罗伦的绝招
It's Roland's special talent.
想要什么 他都可以搞定
Anything you want, he can get it for you.
我会后悔吗？
Am I going to regret this?
只有一个办法知道
There's only one way to find out.
- 走吧 - 不行 由我来骑
- Come on. - No way, I drive.
这晚才刚开始你就想拒绝我？
You really want to start the night by saying no to the girl?
好的
Okay.
我们来做什么？
What am I doing here with you?
庆祝
Celebrating.
你好厉害
You're good at that.
每次问你问题
Every time I ask you a question
你总巧妙地避而不答
you have some clever way of avoiding the answer.
不是那样
That's not true.
举例 你在哪里长大？
Here's an example. Where did you grow up?
看到吗？
See?
为何不谈自己的事？
How come you won't tell me anything about yourself?
我不想扫兴
Because I'm having a nice time and I don't want to ruin it.
那么不可告人吗？
It's that bad, huh?
我宁愿这样
I prefer this.
你说过给我答案
You promised answers.
露西 今天是你生日
Come on, Luce. It's your birthday.
你可能想要其他东西
I'm thinking there's something else you might want.
你做什么？
What are you doing?
- 停 - 我说过让你要远离她
- Stop! - I told you to stay away from her.
丹尼尔 你做什么？
Daniel, what are you doing?
- 为什么？- 因为你很紧张她？停手
- Why, because you care so much about her? - Stop it!
- 停呀 - 不 因为我知道你想怎样
- Stop! - No, because I know what you're capable of.
你仍与路西法为伍 承认吧
You're still with Lucifer. Admit it!
丹尼尔 何不告诉她？告诉她一切
Why don't you tell her, Daniel? Tell her everything.
- 她想知真相 - 停呀
- She wants the truth. - Stop it!
你别再缠着她
Just stay away from her!
这没你说话的份
You don't have a say in it.
我不知道发生了什么事 但与我无关
I don't know what's going on here but it has nothing to do with me.
我从不相信缘份天注定
I never bought into that idea that there's one person you're meant to be with
但那幻觉很真实 感觉亦很真实
but my visions are so real and my feelings are so real
好像前世的经历 我不知道…
it's like past lives or something. I don't know.
所有都跟丹尼尔有关 但他一直避开
And everything's connected to Daniel somehow but he keeps pushing me away.
甘也在隐瞒
And Cam's hiding something too.
你怎么看？
So what do you think?
真可恶 你居然不告诉我你生日
I think you're a jerk for not telling me it was your birthday
但这故事太精彩 所以算数
but I'm willing to overlook that because this is so ridiculously juicy.
你相信前世今生吗？
Do you believe in reincarnation?
不 不信
No. Not at all.
我都不信
I didn't think so either but
但总要有个解释
there has to be some sort of explanation for this.
嗯…
Hmm.
我有办法
Maybe I can help.
你做什么？
What are you doing?
一个人还抢什么
We just need one more thing.
什么？
What?
你怎么知道杜特几号房的？
How do you know which room Todd's in?
怎样操作？
So how does this work exactly?
有带年鉴的照片来吗？
Have you got those yearbook photos?
杜特研究出了这个强大的人脸识别程序
Todd's been working on this really cool facial recognition algorithm.
不全是我的功劳
It's not all my code.
由卡耐基梅隆研发
It was developed at Carnegie Mellon,
我… 稍为调整
but I've tweaked it a little.
他真谦虚
He's so modest.
抱歉
Sorry.
可能要点时间
This might take a minute.
它正在搜索
It's just searching.
露西 过来看看
Luce? Hello?
找到了
We've got hits.
哗
Whoa.
看那名字
Look at the name.
一定是亲戚
It must be a relative.
什么？
Oh, what?
真的… 可恶
The actual... Fuck.
"赫尔斯通 1854"
印出来
Print it.
我去拿
I'll get it.
杜特 我靠你解释给我听了
Todd, I'm counting on you having some sort of explanation
因为我真的很混乱
because I am really struggling here.
我也茫无头绪
I haven't got the faintest idea.
我爱你
I love you.
看看还可以找到什么
Let's see what else we can find.
又来了
It's happening again.
不
No.
不要搞我
Leave me alone!
露西？没事吧？
Luce? Everything okay?
露西？
Luce?
潘妮
Penn!
我要找潘妮
I've gotta find Penn!
潘妮
Penn!
潘妮 你在哪？
Penn, where are you?
杜特
Todd!
我要找潘妮
I've gotta find Penn!
- 不 - 潘妮
- No! - Penn!
杜特
Todd!
不要呀
No!
学校医务室
Here at the school infirmary
跟医院一样会照料周到
we provide the same care she'd receive at the hospital.
我想带她回家
I want to take her home.
医生说她需要临床观察
The doctor's clear. She needs to remain under clinical supervision.
到什么时候？
For how long?
她稳定为止
Until she's stable.
你回去休息一下
You should get some rest.
可以探望露西时我们会通知你的
We'll call you at the hotel as soon as Luce is able to receive visitors.
我们无能为力
There was nothing we could have done.
我无法接受
I refuse to accept that.
我可以警告她 我可以陪着她
I could have warned her. I could have been there...
有用吗？
When has that ever helped?
没关系
It doesn't matter, okay?
她需要我们 是我们负了她
She needs us and we let her down.
是刑事调查？
Is this a criminal investigation?
暂时不是
Not at the moment.
火灾由闪电引起
The fire was caused by lightning.
那是初步报告
That report is preliminary.
鉴于跟崔维尔碧文这件案很相似
Given the similarity to the Trevor Beckman case
我们要盘问她
we'll definitely want to question her.
没律师在场 你不能问她
I don't want you talking to her without her attorney present.
我们今天聚在此地
We come together today
来哀悼我们失去的挚友 他的仁慈慷慨
to mourn the loss of a dear friend, a kind and generous...
短暂的人生
whose life was far too brief to mourn the loss...
他的猝然离世令人悲痛惊讶
whose tragic passing comes as a shock to us all.
我们将永远怀念这位朋友
We will always remember a kind and generous friend
他的陪伴令人快乐
someone whose company was always a pleasure
今天虽然满载悲哀
and although today we are understandably overcome with grief
请相信假以时日
I ask you to have faith that in time
并不会有丝毫减弱
our pain will prove strengthening
并以此来证明
and ultimately a testament
杜特有多重要
to how much Todd mattered
直至永远
and always will.
他不单是个好儿子
Not only was he a loving son
也是仁慈慷慨的朋友
but he was also a kind and generous friend.
我们要将悲哀化为力量
We must transform our sadness into something strengthening.
歌颂他的人生
That's how we celebrate his life
传承他的遗志
and ensure his legacy.
你杀了他然后出席他的丧礼？
You show up to his funeral after you get him killed?
我知道是你做的
I know you're the one doing this.
你说什么？
What are you talking about?
雕像 图书馆失火都是你做的
The statue. The fire in the library.
你想杀她
You were trying to kill her.
杀露西是因为你 丹尼尔
Killing Luce is your thing, Daniel.
你敢…
Don't you dare...
怎么了 丹尼尔？你怕同我争？
What's the matter, Daniel? You afraid of a little competition?
我对露西是真心的
What I feel for Luce is real.
她这次不同 你配不上她
She's different this time. She deserves more than you can give her.
你敢再接近她…
If you come near her...
那又怎么样？
You'll what?
你想目睹她死多少次？
How many times do you have to watch her die?
我爱你
I love you.
露西
Luce!
噢 潘妮
Oh, Penn!
露西
Luce!
杜特呢？
Todd?
对不起
I'm sorry.
对不起 对不起 是我的错
I'm so, so sorry. It's my fault.
别这样说
Oh, don't say that.
是真的 那影子跟之前一模一样
It's true. The shadows were exactly the same.
- 同样是… - 别再说了 好吗？
- It was the exact same... - Stop it, okay?
不是你造成的
You did not cause this.
我不想再听了
I won't hear it.
好吧
Okay.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
许了什么愿？
Did you make a wish?
前世及命运
Past lives and destinies.
你想知道真相
You want the truth.
她完全不记得我了 只需轻轻一吻
She doesn't know me at all. All it takes is a kiss.
但他知道是她
But he knows it's her.
露西 不
Luce! No!
吻了他你便会死掉
Kiss him and you'll die.
谁诅咒他们
Who put the curse on them?
魔鬼本人
It was the devil himself.
丹尼尔 不
Daniel, no!
露西 不
Luce, no.
你会死
You will die.
你好点了吗？
You feeling better?
全身都痛
但是仍活着
Every part of me hurts, but I'm alive.
已经很好了
Well that's something.
我记得…
I remember.
什么？
What?
一切
Everything.
那场火
The fire.
你抱起我
You carrying me.
在你的怀抱里我感觉到…
Being in your arms, it felt like we were...
你有点神志不清
Well you were delirious.
可能是
Maybe.
但我不单记得那件事
But that's not all I remember.
还记得这件事
I remember this.
拍这照片那天
I remember the day this was taken.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
够了
Enough!
我知道一切
I know what I know.
所有人一直都说我疯了
My whole life people have told me that I'm crazy.
露西
Luce.
就看看他们是不是对的
Let's see if they're right.
不 露西 下来
No Luce, get down from there.
别这样 露西
No, Luce.
不要啊
No!
一直都是你 露西
It will always be you, Luce.
一如以往
Just as it always has been.
如今还不是伤春悲秋的时候
Now is not the time for sentimentality.
露西？
Luce?
是我送给你的
I gave you this.
很久以前…
It was a long time ago.
怎么可能？
How is this possible?
- 没事的 - 不 发生在我身上
- It's okay. - No, every bad thing
的厄运都是它造成的
that's ever happened to me is because of that.
它们不会伤害你 只会观察
No, they can't hurt you. They just observe.
那场火 它杀了崔维尔
The fires. They killed Trevor.
露西 那场火不是影子或你引起的
Luce, the shadows didn't cause the fire and neither did you.
它们叫 "宣告者"
They're called Announcers.
看
Look.
就当是过去之窗
Think of them as windows into the past.
它们被你人生的重要时刻所吸引
They're attracted to the most important moments in your life.
这影像是什么？
What am I seeing?
我们在一起生活过的时光
Our lives together.
我们相爱了几千年
We've been in love for thousands of years.
露西 你所有幻觉都是真的
Luce, all your visions are real.
我们转世重生？
So we're reincarnated?
你是
You are.
但我是…
I'm...
天使
An angel.
其中一个折翼天使
I'm one of the Fallen.
停啊
Stop!
不要 露西
Don't do it, Luce.
吻他你便会死去
Kiss him and you will die.
所以我设法阻止你 但没有成功
This is why I tried so hard to push you away but I can't.
你没告诉她？
You didn't tell her?
对不起
I'm so sorry.
难以置信 你太过份了
Unbelievable. You're unbelievable.
什么？我不明白
What? I don't understand, why?
诅咒是惩罚我拒绝选边站
The curse is my punishment for not taking a side at the Fall.
露西 别听他
Luce, don't listen to him.
留下来 露西 我选择你
Stay, Luce. I chose you.
我选择爱
I chose love.
露西 别听他的说话
Don't listen to him, Luce.
吻他你便会死掉
If you kiss him, you will die.
- 我亲眼见过几千次 - 不 这次不同
- I've seen it a thousand times. - No, this time it's different.
我保证
I promise it is different.
他是谎话精 露西
He's a liar, Luce.
跟我一起 我会保护你的
If you stay with me, I can protect you.
你看过我的真身
You've seen me in my true form.
这次不同了
This is different.
我可以保护你
I can protect you.
我们有这机会
This could be our chance.
求求你
Please.
露西 跟我才有将来
Luce, I can offer you a future.
有人生
A life.
我不能再失去你了
I can't lose you again.
我知道自己想要什么
I know what I want.
不要啊
No!
我还没有死啊
I'm still here.
你以为已经打破了诅咒？
You think you've beaten the curse?
你懵然不知道自己身处的险境
You have no idea how much danger she's in.
路西法知道她还没受洗
Lucifer knows she's not baptized.
我不明白 究竟什么事？
I don't understand. Tell me why.
对他的诅咒已经解除 对你的还没有
He lifted the curse for himself, not for you.
他会来对付她
He'll come for her now.
丹尼尔不能保护你了 露西
Daniel can't protect you, Luce.
我可以
I can!
她跟我安全点
She's safer with me!
丹尼尔 凡事都有规律
There's a natural order to things, Daniel.
你不能任意妄为
You can't just do as you please.
宿命已被打破
Well the cycle's been broken.
罗伦 莫莉
Roland! Molly!
露西
Luce!
你跟我来
You're coming with me!
保护她 我要对付甘
Keep her safe. I need to deal with Cam.
我不想他跟着我们
Where I'm taking her, I don't want him to follow.
他会引路西法来的
He'll lead Lucifer right to us.
他们全都是天使…
They're all angels.
我不会让你把带她到路西法那
I won't let you take her to Lucifer!
我不再听命于他
I don't answer to him anymore.
是你令她陷入险境 丹尼尔
You're the one putting her in danger, Daniel.
别假扮关心她
Don't pretend you even care about her!
你去哪里？
Where are you going?
我可以保护她
I can protect her.
别碰她
Stay away from her!
搞什么鬼
What the heck!
回房去 关上门
Back to your rooms. Shut the door!
全面封锁
This is a lockdown.
直至一切正常
Wait for the all clear.
封锁 关门
It's a lockdown. Shut the door.
- 别怕 - 我不怕
- Don't be afraid. - I'm not.
我不是你的敌人
I'm not your enemy.
我没想过要杀她
I'm not trying to kill her.
那么是谁？
Then who?
露西 等等
Luce! Wait!
她在图书馆放火 是她…
She set the fire in the library. She...
潘妮
Penn?
不要
No!
不要啊
去吧
Go!
露西 时间到了 我厌倦了等待
Luce, your time has come. I am tired of waiting.
如今完结吧
This ends now.
你的呼吸令丹尼尔无法返回天堂
Every breath you take keeps Daniel from his rightful place in heaven!
- 丹尼尔 - 你才是诅咒
- Daniel! - You are the real curse.
露西
Luce!
苏菲亚 你做了什么？
Sophia, what have you done?
还自称是神的仆人
You claim to be a servant of God.
我是战争在进行时
I am. There's a war going on.
忠诚的士兵要尽自己的本份
Loyal soldiers do what they must.
所以要杀人？
Including murder?
你拒绝为大局着想
You refuse to see the bigger picture.
你一直如此
You always have.
她一死 你被迫要选择
With her gone you'd have been forced to choose a side
规律便可恢复
and order would have been restored.
谢谢你
Thank you.
她为何要这样做？
I don't understand why she'd do that.
她是狂热份子 露西
She's a fanatic, Luce.
她为神而战斗 但过了火
She fights for god, but she went too far.
苏菲亚为何要杀潘妮？
Why would Sophia kill Penn?
为何要杀我？
Why did she try to kill me?
你没有受洗 死了便是永恒
You're not baptized. If you die, it'll be forever.
她以为你死了 我便不再留恋人间
Sophia thought with you gone I'd have no reason to stay on earth
便会返回天堂
and I'd return to heaven.
但甘说得对
But Cam was right.
路西法会来对付你的
Lucifer will be coming for you.
所以我要带你去安全的地方
Which is why I need to get you somewhere safe.
有个地方 我有朋友在 可以保护我们
I know a place. I have friends there. They'll protect us.
我们要走了
We have to go.
我不能走 不能丢下潘妮
I can't leave now. I can't leave Penn.
我们可以照顾她的
We'll take care of her.
潘妮
Penn!
她会跟我们走的 去吧
She'll come with us. Go. Please.
露西
Luce.
她们会带潘妮走
They'll take Penn with them.
没时间了 我们要走了
There's no more time. We have to go.
等等 听我说
Wait a minute. Listen.
我的一生都在寻找真相
My whole life I've been searching for the truth.
我想知道我究竟是谁
I've been trying to figure out who I am.
为何我总是格格不入
Why I never seem to fit in to the life that was supposed to be mine.
如今我很害怕
And now I'm terrified.
我现在有更多的问题
I have more questions than I ever have before
但… 就是这样
but... this is it.
这就是我
This is who I am.
这就是我的归宿
This is where I belong.
在这儿 跟你一起
Right here, with you.
我爱你
I love you.
第一眼看到你我就知道
I've known it from the first moment I saw you.
一直都是你 露西
It will always be you, Luce.
永远都是
Forever.
折翼天使首部曲：魔咒之吻